benefitbar.com 2012-11-20

# BenefitBar.com

Home > Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

**_Your Privacy Rights_**

**Corporate**

This Privacy Policy applies to BenefitBar hosted Web sites or Web sites hosted by third parties on behalf of Benefitbar, which are branded to appear like Benefitbar. Please visit www.benefitbar.com for more information. 

**1.0 Personal Information**

As a leader in toolbar technology, BenefitBar understands your desire to protect personal information. We intend to inform you of how your personal information will be gathered, tracked or used, and to give you choices. 

**What Information We Gather and Track**

We request personal information when you correspond with us or engage in certain other activities on our Web site. For example, if you request technical support online, we will ask you for information necessary to complete the transaction, such as your confirmation number and information about your computer hardware, software and the nature of the problem you are experiencing. 

You make the decision whether to proceed with any activity that requests personal information. If you do not wish to provide the requested information, however, you may not be able to complete the transaction. 

**How We Use the Information We Gather and Track**

We use personally identifiable information in the following ways: 

1\. To provide you with information about product upgrades and renewal information every 12 months; 

2\. To assist us in creating better products and services to meet your needs; 

**With Whom We May Share Your Information**

BenefitBar may retain the services of outside contractors to provide services for us. They may be used to provide technical support or handle order processing. We require that these contractors keep the personal information of customers secure and confidential. We also require that these contractors use personal information only on behalf of BenefitBar. 

Please be advised that in certain instances, it may be necessary for Benefitbar to disclose your personal information to government officials or otherwise as required by our legal obligations. 

**Refer-A-Friend**

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. BenefitBar does not store your friend's name and email address after sending the one-time email. 

1.1 Security and Quality of Personal Information 

We have taken security measures, consistent with international information practices, to protect your personal information. These measures include technical and procedural steps to protect your data from misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, loss, alteration or destruction. Credit card information is transmitted using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption. 

We make a sincere effort to respond to your requests to update or correct your personal information. If you believe that BenefitBar does not have your current personal information, you can update it at www.benefitbar.com. 

**1.2 Links to Business Partner**

At the BenefitBar Web site, there are a number of links to companies with whom we have a relationship. BenefitBar is not responsible for the privacy practices of our business partners. We encourage you to read their privacy statements, as they may differ from ours. 

**1.3 Other Privacy Considerations**

Please remember that information you submit in a discussion group or forum will be deemed public information and is not confidential. There is a risk in such communication venues that information can be collected and used by others. Please be careful and responsible when you are online. 

**1.4 Policy Changes**

In the event that there is a major change to BenefitBar's privacy practices, a prominent notice will be posted on our Web site. If the change involves the use of your personally identifiable information, the notice will contain instructions on how you can opt-out of such use. 

**1.5 BenefitBar Contact Information**

BenefitBar has designated a Privacy Officer who is accountable for Benefitbar's compliance with the privacy practices described in this policy. If you have any questions or comments concerning this policy, or if you would like to change your communication preferences, update or review the personal information we have about you, or withdraw your consent for the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information, please contact us using one of the options below: 

BenefitBar.com 

Email: privacy (at) benefitbar (dot) com
